http://www.himmelstein.com/privacy-policy

Introduction
Your privacy is important to S. Himmelstein and Company (“Himmelstein”). We collect information to provide and deliver better service and customized content to our Registered Users. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand how we collect and use your information. S. Himmelstein and Company is committed to protecting the privacy of its registered users and other contacts.
Scope
This Privacy Policy applies to all personal data processed by full-time and part-time employees, contractors, and partners doing business on behalf of S. Himmelstein and Company, and business processes conducted by S. Himmelstein and Company.
Definition of Terms
Specific to this Privacy Policy, we make reference to various business terms to describe our commercial activity. We define such terms as follows:
Affiliate: An advertising partner of S. Himmelstein and Company.
Customer: An organization that interacts with S. Himmelstein and Company.
Registered User: A user that has registered for information about S. Himmelstein and Company’s products or services.
Third-Party Content: White papers, data, and other documents owned by content providers and made available to S. Himmelstein and Company’s audience.
Information We Collect
Our services require you to register with S. Himmelstein and Company. This includes general site registration, webinar registration, downloading S. Himmelstein and Company content, and participating in our surveys. When you become a Registered User with S. Himmelstein and Company, we collect the following personal data:
Name and contact details
User name
Password
Company name and address
Country
Job function
Industry
Authentication data
Location data
Time zone
Other information you provide to us
How We Use Information We Collect
S. Himmelstein and Company uses your personal information for the following purposes:
To provide support or other services.
S. Himmelstein and Company may use your personal information to provide you with support that you have requested. S. Himmelstein and Company may also use your personal information to respond directly to your requests for information, including newsletter subscriptions, webinar registrations, to forward your contact information to the appropriate resource for follow-up related to your interests, and other support requests.
To provide information based on your needs and respond to your requests
S. Himmelstein and Company may use your personal information to provide you with new products, notices of new or enhanced products, product updates or releases, website features, or service developments.
To select content, improve quality, and facilitate use of our website
S. Himmelstein and Company may use your personal information, including the information gathered as a result of site navigation and electronic protocols and cookies (including third-party cookies), to help create and deliver personalized content, improve website quality, track marketing campaign responsiveness, evaluate page response rates, conduct usability testing, and facilitate your use of our websites (for example, to facilitate navigation and the login process, avoid duplicate data entry, enhance security, and preserve information between sessions).
To communicate with you about a webinar
We may communicate with you about a webinar. This may include information about the content, logistics, updates, and additional information related to the webinar.
Engagement with third-parties
S. Himmelstein and Company will not share your personal data with third-parties.
To get feedback or input from you
In order to deliver products and services of the most interest to you, from time to time, we may ask you to provide us with input and feedback (for example, through surveys, usability studies, and focus groups).
Disclosure of Personal Information
When you become a Registered User with S. Himmelstein and Company, your contact information and registration details will not be shared with anyone other than S. Himmelstein and Company and its employees. Information you provide when registering for, or participating in, a webinar or downloading a white paper, may be used to contact you in a manner that is common within our industry, e.g., contacting you with product information or to assess your interest in our products and services. The treatment of such information is subject to our privacy policies. We may contact you after the white paper download or webinar regarding updates or regarding related products and services. You should contact us directly if you have any questions about our use of your information.
How Can You Control Your Information?
S. Himmelstein and Company will only use your profile information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or subsequently authorized by you. If you do not want your information disclosed in this way, you must not opt-in to receive e-mails from us.
Users who prefer not to provide data requested for any of our registration processes do not need to opt-in with us. You can still view the content and use some of the services offered by our site without registering, certain services may not be available to you.
We provide to users the option to opt-in or opt-out of receiving our email newsletters, Product Alerts, webinar promotional invitations, or emails. Users who opt-in may also remove themselves from our email lists at any time through the edit profile pages or by following the instructions at the end of any email received from S. Himmelstein and Company.
You can control the information we have about you and how we use it in several ways:
Access and Updating of Information
If you have opted-in to receive e-mails from S. Himmelstein and Company, you may change your information at any time and as often as necessary by sending an email to: news@himmestein.com.
Protect Your Information
Remember to close your browser window when you have finished using our site. This will prevent others from accessing your profile information, e.g., instances where you may share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or internet café.
To contact us regarding a privacy issue, please send an e-mail to news@himmelstein.com. Where applicable, please be sure to include the site, newsletter, Product Alert or product so that we may better serve you.
Technical Information
We collect information about the services you use and how you use them (e.g., viewing a technical video, visiting a page on our site, or reading an article in the News section). This information includes:
Device Information
We collect device-specific information (e.g., hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information).
Logging Practices
S. Himmelstein and Company automatically records the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors. The IP address is a unique number assigned to every computer on the internet. Generally, an IP address changes each time you connect to the internet (it is a "dynamic" address). Note, however, that if you have a broadband connection, depending on your individual circumstance, the IP address that we collect may contain information that could be deemed identifiable. This is because, with some broadband connections, your IP address doesn't change (it is "static") and could be associated with your personal computer.
We track pages visited on S. Himmelstein and Company’s website, the amount of time spent on those pages, and the types of searches done on them.
S. Himmelstein and Company also captures and stores information that you transmit. This may include:
Browser/Device type/version
Operating system used
Media Access Control (MAC) address
Date and time of the server request
Volume of data transferred
Unique Application Numbers
Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be stored by S. Himmelstein and Company.
Local Storage
We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on our device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and CRMs.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Cookies and web beacons are electronic placeholders that are placed on your device by websites to track your individual movements on that website over time. S. Himmelstein and Company uses both session-based cookies (which last only for the duration of the user's session) and persistent cookies (which remain on your device and provides information about the session you are in and waits for the next time you use that site again).
These cookies and web beacons provide useful information to S. Himmelstein and Company, enabling us to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's access to and use of our sites, allows us to track usage behavior, and to balance the usage of our websites on all S. Himmelstein and Company web servers.
Tracking cookies and other technologies such as web beacons may be used to process additional information, enable non-core functionalities on the S. Himmelstein and Company website and enable third-party functions (such as a social media "share" link). We may also include web beacons and other similar technology in promotional email messages to determine whether the messages have been opened.
Third-Party and Co-branded Web Sites
The S. Himmelstein and Company website may contain links to other websites. S. Himmelstein and Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our site and review the privacy statements of each website they visit that collects information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by S. Himmelstein and Company.
Disclosure of Anonymous, Aggregated Information
S. Himmelstein and Company does not provide summary reports to other third-party suppliers, advertisers, and service providers.
Legal and Regulatory Information
Personal Data about Minors and Children
S. Himmelstein and Company does not knowingly collect data from or about children under sixteen (16) years of age without the permission of parent(s)/guardian(s). If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under age 16, please contact us.
Collaboration with Authorities
S. Himmelstein and Company has appointed and mandated a privacy officer who represents the regulatory authorities inside the S. Himmelstein and Company organization, and in return represents the S. Himmelstein and Company organization to regulatory authorities.
The S. Himmelstein and Company privacy officer will ensure proper communication with the relevant regulatory authority for privacy. The privacy officer will lead investigative action, complaint handling, and data breach notification. The privacy officer will also monitor regulatory changes and consult the regulatory authority where implementation of a regulatory or technological change leads to doubt.
S. Himmelstein and Company reserves the right to share your information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law.
Transfer of Information to Other Countries
As a global organization, S. Himmelstein and Company engages in a number of international activities. In connection with the management of those activities, S. Himmelstein and Company may transfer information to other countries. By submitting your information to S. Himmelstein and Company via our websites, or in connection with your interactions with S. Himmelstein and Company offline, you consent to such transfers and to the processing of this information in other countries.
Your California Privacy Rights
Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (also known as S.B. 27), if you are a California resident and your business relationship with S. Himmelstein and Company is primarily for personal, family, or household purposes, you may request certain data regarding S. Himmelstein and Company’s disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to news@himmelstein.com with "Request for California Privacy Information" in the subject line. You may make such a request up to once per calendar year. If applicable, we will provide you, by email, a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the third parties' names and addresses. Please note that not all personal information sharing is covered by S.B. 27's requirements.
Your European Union Privacy Rights
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation EU 2016/679) (also known as GDPR), if you are an individual protected by the GDPR you may have certain rights as a data subject. To request information about or avail yourself of those rights, please send an email to news@himmelstein.com with "GDPR Request" in the subject line. In the email please describe, with specificity, the GDPR right you are requesting assistance with. Please note additional information may be requested prior to initiation of a request and that S. Himmelstein and Company reserves the right to charge a fee with respect to certain requests. Upon S. Himmelstein and Company’s completion of its review, you will be notified if your request has been granted, denied, or exemptions apply.
Business Transfers
If all or part of S. Himmelstein and Company is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, the profile information and activity data that you have provided to us may be transferred as part of that transaction.
How Will You Know If Our Privacy Policy Has Changed?
S. Himmelstein and Company, in its sole discretion, reserves the right to update its Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email if you have an S. Himmelstein and Company account, or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact:
If you have any questions about the policy, you can write to:
Wheel Torque Sensors (Torque Wheels)
